Revenge is a funny thing.
Ocean's Thirteen is a crime, thriller film directed by Steven Soderbergh.
Danny Ocean's team of criminals are back and
composing a plan more personal than ever.
When ruthless casino owner Willy Bank doublecrosses Reuben Tishkoff, causing a heart attack, Danny Ocean vows
that he and his team will do anything to bring down Willy Bank along with everything he's got.
Even if it means asking for help from an enemy.
Danny Ocean, played by George Clooney.
Rusty Ryan, played by Brad Pitt.
Willy Bank, played by Al Pacino.
Linus Caldwell, played by Matt Damon.
Basher Tarr, played by Don Cheadle.
Frank Catton, played by Bernie Mac.
Ocean's Thirteen (stylized as Ocean's 13) is a 2007 American heist comedy film directed
by Steven Soderbergh and written by Brian Koppelman and David Levien.
It is the third film in the Ocean's trilogy.
The film features an ensemble cast including George Clooney, Brad Pitt, Matt Damon,
Andy García, Don Cheadle, Bernie Mac, Ellen Barkin and Al Pacino.
Filming began in July 2006 in Las Vegas and Los Angeles.
It was screened as an Out of Competition presentation at the 2007 Cannes Film Festival on May 24,
2007, and was theatrically released in the United States on June 8 by Warner Bros.
It received generally positive reviews from critics
and grossed $312 million worldwide.
The film explores themes of casino, heart attack,
con man, master thief, hidden camera.
The tone is intense.